http://www.sevenmeadowsarchery.com/privacy-policy.html

Seven Meadows Archery
Home
Bows
SPECIALS!!
Privacy Policy & Terms
Information We Collect:When ordering products from our site you will be asked to enter your name, email phone, shipping and billing information.  We do not keep payment information on file.We implement a variety of security measure to maintain the safety of your personal information.We do not accept credit card numbers delivered by e-mail.  You should never send credit card information by email, as it is not secure.Cookies Like many other websites, SevenMeadowsArchery.com uses a standard technology called "cookies." Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored on your hard drive and not on our site. They can help make your Internet experience quicker and more convenient. Cookies let you keep shopping cart information independent from our servers. They help us understand how customers use our service, which allows us to improve and tailor the service. You will not be able to use the  SevenMeadowsArchery.com  service if you disable cookies.Disclosure of Information:We do not sell, trade or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree t keep this information confidential.  We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce  our site policies or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.  This policy was last modified  12/6/18.Contact us:If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the following information:Seven Meadows Inc.6634 S. Alder St.Tacoma, WA  98409USAbows@sevenmeadowsarchery.com
pci_dss_self_assessment_certificate__2_.pdfFile Size:
166 kbFile Type:
SPECIALS!!
